FRANCISCO PEREIRA

Degree in Informatics Engineering



- Portugal
- +351 926 843 295
- @ franciscoandre.farp@gmail.com
- ffarps.github.io
 - linkedin.com/francisco-pereira

OBJECTIVE

My name is Francisco André Rodrigues Pereira, I'm 21 years old, from Mirandela, and I have a degree in Computer Engineering from the Polytechnic Institute of Bragança,

During the third year of the course and after completing it, I was awarded two research grants by the Centre for Research in Digitalisation and Intelligent Robotics (CeDRI).

I'm currently developing some personal projects related to areas I'm interested in, in order to develop a portfolio in the future

Proactive and dedicated, ready to achieve great things.

EXPERIENCE

Jul 2023-Sep 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Contributed to an OpenZDM project related to the development of a tool that aims to reduce defects in production chains in a car factory in the assembly and *body shop* zones.

Jul 2022-Jan 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Worked on developing Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) apps in Unity, using different frameworks and tools, such as MRTK, ARCore, Vuforia SDK and ARFoundation.

Oct 2021-Feb 2022 Scientific Initiation Internship

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Written a scientific paper "Cybersecurity Threat Modeling and Enhancement of Intrusion Detection System in Cyber-physical Conveyor System".

EDUCATION

Oct 2019-Jul 2023 Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineering

Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Computer Science, Computer Engineering, Mathematics, Information Systems.

Worked on many projects related to Web Development, Computer Architecture, Networking, 3D Modeling, Machine Learning, Data Structures, SQL and IoT.

2016-2019 High School Diploma

Science and technology

Agrupamento de Escolas de Mirandela

LANGUAGES

Portuguese - native English - proficient

HARD SKILLS

- · Unity 3D
- C#, C, Python, Java, Javascript, Rust, etc
- Git
- Linux
- · SQL
- Cloud

SOFT SKILLS

- · Self-taught
- · Attention to detail
- Technical Writing
- Teamwork